[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the special talent of Alex the Lion from the 2008 animated comedy movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "He can dance.", "incorrect_answers": ["He can run really fast.", "He can sing.", "He can paint."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg wrote the movie Superbad and named the two main characters Seth and Evan.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Harry die in Alfred Hitchcocks 1955 movie The Trouble with Harry?", "correct_answer": "From natural causes", "incorrect_answers": ["Captain Albert Wiles shot him.", "Miss Ivy Gravely killed him with her hiking boot.", "He committed suicide."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the set of real numbers under the operation of multiplication, every number has an inverse.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a hydrometer?", "correct_answer": "An instrument used to measure a liquids density", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "An instrument used to measure a liquids temperature", "An instrument used to measure a liquids weight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By law German beer can only be made from these four ingredients:", "correct_answer": "Water, hops, malted barley, yeast", "incorrect_answers": ["Water, hops, malted wheat, carbon dioxide", "Water, hops, malt, citric acid", "Water, hops, malt, sugar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Much of the Soylent Greens music came from classical composers. Which of these composers\u2019 music was not used on the movie?", "correct_answer": "Wagner", "incorrect_answers": ["Tchaikovsky", "Grieg", "Beethoven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following groups of mammals lay eggs?", "correct_answer": "Monotremes", "incorrect_answers": ["Rodentia", "Marsupials", "Chiroptera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first nation to adopt a metric system?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "Austria", "Vatican City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a Russian tradition of spitting three times to chase away bad luck, similar to knocking on wood. Where should one spit?", "correct_answer": "Over their left shoulder", "incorrect_answers": ["In front of their feet", "Over their right shoulder", "Through their crossed fingers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much is Triceratops thought to have weighed?", "correct_answer": "Between 13,000 and 26,000 lbs", "incorrect_answers": ["Between 1,000 and 9,000 lbs", "Between 50,000 and 75,000 lbs", "Between 110,000 and 140,000 lbs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the Separatist leader in Star Wars episodes one to three?", "correct_answer": "Newt Gunray", "incorrect_answers": ["Haako", "Rute Gunnay", "San Hill"]}]